

Hamza Saeed

Nationality: Pakistani Date of birth: 18/08/1998

Caree 1 Phone number: (+49) 1778741500

Email address: saeedhamza268@gmail.com

• Home: Kurt-Schumacher 32, Apartment 325, 67663 Kaiserslautern (Germany)

ABOUT ME

Front end developer with an experience of creating effective websites that give users an immersive and interesting experience. Through my precise and efficient coding, which I was trained about, I have been attempting to fully meet user expectations. I'm determined to enhance my skills, So I can provide best of me. I don't see perfection in me but I always try to deliver best of me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web developer

Ideatech Software House [01/06/2019 - 31/12/2019]

City: Islamabad **Country:** Pakistan

- Performed fully dynamic and browser compatible pages with the help of HTML5, CSS3, jQuery and lavaScript.
- Improving user experience and delivering in smoother operations.
- Got experience in building single page application (SPA), flexible web design UI with the help of HTML5 and CSS3.
- Helped Senior developers in order to tackles bugs and produce effective website performance.

Front-end Developer

SOFIT Consultancy (Pvt.) Ltd [01/11/2018 – 31/05/2019]

City: Rawalpindi **Country:** Pakistan

- Developed frontend of websites using JavaScript and its frameworks like Angular.Js and Ext.Js.
- Produced eye-catching website interfaces by converting UI/UX design frameworks into code with the help of implementing HTML5 and CSS3.
- · Also worked with Back End developers, to get an idea about back end developing

Cyber security Internship

National Center of Cyber Security Air University Islamabad [25/06/2018 – 05/10/2018]

City: Islamabad **Country:** Pakistan

- Worked with National Cybercrime and Forensics Lab as Mobile Forensics intern.
- I learned how to work with Linux (installation, commands etc) and how to manage projects on github during the span.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science in Computer Sciences

Air University [01/06/2016 – 13/08/2020]

Address: Service Road E-9 / E-8, 44000 Islamabad (Pakistan), 44230 Islamabad (Pakistan)

Website: https://www.au.edu.pk/

• I have done Bachelor of Science in Computer Sciences from Air University Islamabad, Pakistan

Master in Information Technology

Altinbas University [01/11/2020 - Current]

Address: Mahmutbey, Dilmenler Cd. No:26,, 34217 Istanbul (Turkey), 34217 Istanbul (Turkey)

Website: https://international.altinbas.edu.tr/en/

• I have started Masters degree in Information Technology from Altinbas University Turkey Istanbul.

Master degree thesis

Technical University of Kaiserslautern [01/04/2020 – Current]

Address: Erwin-Schrödinger-Straße 52, 67663 Kaiserslautern (Germany), 67663 Kaiserslautern (Germany)

Website: https://www.uni-kl.de/

• I have completed my Masters degree subjects from Altinbas University Istanbul then I came to Technical University of Kaiserslautern, Germany to carry on my thesis work.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Urdu

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

DIGITAL SKILLS

Web Development (HTML5, CSS, JavaScript) / Basic React JS Angular JS / Graphic Designer / Adobe Illustrator / Adobe after effects / Blender / Adobe Photoshop

MY PORTFOLIO

Portfolio of my work

• You are welcome to see my digital portfolio, I which I have shared some of my past work.

Link: https://hamzaasaeed.netlify.app/